The new Kajambe that fans have been waiting for is here! After my hard work this week,
The test was finally launched today. This project cost a lot of money and consumed a lot of energy. Not much to say,
Start watching directly. This is the V3 version of our uncle Kajambe, with added damaged, almost new,
The headgear and accessories were updated in real time, and then the armor was changed to the real-time amount.
Then the time is updated every ten minutes. Now there is still a flaw, just because of time.
Therefore, accessories cannot be ignored now.
Now the price difference between combat readiness and combat readiness has been added to the interface.
Then replace the original fake account and the non-fake account with the addition and subtraction of the amount, and then refresh it.
It is updated very quickly now, now it is updated every ten minutes.
Of course, you can now see 110,000, 180,000,
The times for 350,000 are updated differently. There will be a one-minute interval in between.
This is normal. Generally speaking, they will be updated gradually. For example,
For example, this one with 780,000 yuan now has 64,000 yuan, and the current level 5 head is almost brand new.
Can get stuck a lot. Like before, this cannot be calculated.
This is our V3 version, which is still in internal testing. Usually updated every ten minutes.
The algorithm is the same as before, all are based on spending the least Huff Coin and getting as close to the card station as possible.
Okay, this is our black and red list of the extended range function, almost total loss and no loss of helmet armor.
This is to tell you in more detail where the first helmet and armor can get stuck.
And with this interface, I know there are many people like me.
When there was still a little money left, there was no way to know how much Jihu’s new and damaged combat readiness was.
At that time, this function will be able to help you a lot, and then tell you which new Jihu brand has the most fake accounts.
Or which place can better suit your combat preparations. Of course, armor also has this function.
But when it comes to armor, there are generally no false accounts, they are all B-A. Through this,
You can tell which armor has the lowest fake account, right? The cost is huge,
All it needs is your attention.